

## **Profile**

Full Stack Developer at Tietoevry Care, specializing in cloud-native, AI-powered healthcare solutions. Contributed to Finland's largest healthcare data platform (HUS DataLake), improving data accessibility. Proficient in React, TypeScript, GraphQL, Node.js, Docker, Kubernetes, Terraform, and Azure Cloud. Worked on LLM-based AI prototypes, including a demo at ICT Days and a diagnostic tool piloted at the New Children's Hospital for faster symptom-based searches.

# **Employment History**

## Full Stack Developer, Tietoevry, Espoo

JUNE 2023 - PRESENT

Developing cloud-native, AI-powered healthcare applications for Finland's largest healthcare providers. Working with React, TypeScript, Node.js, GraphQL-, PostgreSQL, Docker, Kubernetes, Terraform, Azure Cloud and Azure DevOps in Agile Scrum teams.

## **Key contributions:**

- Contributing to the <u>HUS DataLake</u> platform for real-time healthcare data access
- Built an <u>AI PoC</u> to assist doctors in faster diagnosis via medical document analysis
- Developed an <u>LLM-based Al solution for ICT Days</u>, Finland's largest healthcare tech event

## Junior Full Stack Developer, Anyhau, Espoo

DECEMBER 2022 - APRIL 2023

Worked on a greenfield web <u>application for booking animal-related services</u>, in collaboration with the 2022 Diili show winner. For providers to list services, and customers to book & pay online. Used **Next.js**, **Typscript**, **Material UI**, and **MongoDB**.

# Education

# Computer Programming, Hive Helsinki, Helsinki

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

Completed a project-based program focused on teamwork, problem-solving, and self-directed learning. Built skills in collaboration, critical thinking, and adaptability for real-world software development.

Interesting projects which I am proud of:

- My <u>most favourite</u> project is made in a group of four people. A re-creation of Netflix - <u>Hypertube</u>
- My second favourite project is made in duo, full-stack, a re-creation of Tinder -Matcha
- My third is made in solo, full-stack, a re-creation of Instagram, fully functional and deployed! <u>CHECK OUT</u>

## A2 finnish language skill, SataEdu, Rauma

NOVEMBER 2016 - JULY 2017

Self-studied Finnish after school now converse comfortably and keep improving.

# **Certificate**

### Azure Fundamentals AZ-900, Microsoft

JULY 2023 - AUGUST 2023

### **Personal Details**

Espoo Finland +35844-989-4822 gaborulenius@gmail.com

### Links

My Portfolio Linkedin GitHub Mangofruit - Live project

### **Technical skills / Programming**

### Languages

React, Next.js, Node.js

Typescript

GraphQL

HTML5, CSS, Javascript Vanilla

PHP

C

MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, MariaDB

Terraform

### **Soft Skills**

Teamwork

**Creative Problem Solving** 

**Critical Thinking** 

Communication

Growth Mindset

Adaptability

Accountability

**Customer Service** 

Efficiency

Time management

Organization & rigor

#### Tools

Azure DevOps, Azure Cloud GitHub, Gitlab & Git, CI/CD pipelines Docker Kubernetes Asana, Atlassian, Jira, Confluence, Miro MAMP, XAMPP, LAMP MyphpAdmin, pgAdmin, DataGrip, Postico 2, DBeaver Mongoose Postman Lucidchart Bulma, MUI, Tailwind Redux, Recoil, Jotai VS Code, Vim, CLI, Termux,